<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?mso-application progid="Excel.Sheet"?>
<Workbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
  xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office"
  xmlns:x="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"
  xmlns:ss="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
  xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40">
  <ExcelWorkbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"/>
  <Styles>
    <Style ss:ID="s25">
      <Font x:CharSet="204" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Bold="1"/>
      <Interior ss:Color="#00FF00" ss:Pattern="Solid"/>
      <NumberFormat ss:Format="#,##0"/>
    </Style>
    <Style ss:ID="s26">
      <Font x:CharSet="204" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Bold="1"/>
      <Interior ss:Color="#FFFF99" ss:Pattern="Solid"/>
      <Alignment ss:Horizontal="Center" ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
    </Style>
    <Style ss:ID="s20">
      <Alignment ss:Horizontal="Center" ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
    </Style>
    <Style ss:ID="s21">
      <Font x:CharSet="204" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Bold="1"/>
    </Style>
    <Style ss:ID="s22">
      <Alignment ss:Horizontal="Center" ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
      <NumberFormat ss:Format="#,##0"/>
    </Style>
    <Style ss:ID="s23">
      <Alignment ss:Horizontal="Center" ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
    </Style>
  </Styles>
  <Worksheet ss:Name="LocStuff">
    <Table>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">KEY</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">ORIGINAL TEXT</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">TRANSLATED TEXT</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">CHARACTER LIMIT</Data>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632410</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Assist Mikhaila Ilyushin</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Допомогти Катерині Ільюшиній</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632411</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Mikhaila mentioned that Lan Nguyen in Power Plant might know how to help restore power to the subsection of the station where her office is. I should locate Lan or what&apos;s left of her.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Катерина сказала, що Лан Нгуєн, яка перебуває на електростанції, може допомогти мені відновити подачу енергії в ту частину станції, де розташований її кабінет. Мені потрібно знайти Лан — або те, що від неї залишилося.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632412</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Chief systems engineer Mikhaila Ilyushin is hiding in the coolant monitoring room of the Power Plant.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Головна системна інженерка Катерина Ільюшина ховається на електростанції в кімнаті моніторингу систем охолодження.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632413</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Chief systems engineer Mikhaila Ilyushin is hiding in the coolant monitoring room of the Power Plant. She suffers from a rare neurological condition called Paraplexis and will die soon without the booster shots in her office.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Головна системна інженерка Катерина Ільюшина ховається на електростанції в кімнаті моніторингу систем охолодження. У неї рідкісна хвороба, парапраксія, і вона помре, якщо не отримає ліки, які зберігаються в її кабінеті.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632414</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Chief systems engineer Mikhaila Ilyushin is hiding in the coolant monitoring room of the Power Plant. She suffers from a rare neurological condition called Paraplexis and will die soon without the booster shots I found in her office.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Головна системна інженерка Катерина Ільюшина ховається на електростанції в кімнаті моніторингу систем охолодження. У неї рідкісна хвороба, парапраксія, і вона помре, якщо не отримає ліки, знайдені мною в її кабінеті.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632415</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Chief systems engineer Mikhaila Ilyushin is hiding in the coolant monitoring room of the Power Plant. She suffers from a rare neurological condition called Paraplexis and will die soon without the booster shots in her office. Unfortunately, her office has no power and is exposed to vacuum. I&apos;d have to fix - or replace - the grounding resistor to get power out to that section again. Then I&apos;d be able to open doors out there and see where I&apos;m going. Lan Nguyen mentioned spare resistors in Parts Storage in the Coolant Chamber.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Головний системний інженер Катерина Ільюшина ховається на електростанції, у кімнаті моніторингу систем охолодження. У неї рідкісна хвороба, парапраксія, і вона помре, якщо не отримає ліки, які зберігаються в її кабінеті. На жаль, у її кабінеті немає електрики і він розгерметизований. Мені потрібно полагодити або замінити заземлювальний резистор, щоб відновити енергопостачання в тій частині станції. Тоді я зможу відчиняти двері і бачити, куди йду. Лан Нгуєн згадувала, що запасні резистори зберігаються на складі деталей у камері з теплоносієм.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632416</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Chief systems engineer Mikhaila Ilyushin is hiding in the coolant monitoring room of the Power Plant. She suffers from a rare neurological condition called Paraplexis and will die soon without the booster shots in her office. Unfortunately, her office has no power and is exposed to vacuum.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Головна системна інженерка Катерина Ільюшина ховається на електростанції в кімнаті моніторингу систем охолодження. У неї рідкісна хвороба, парапраксія, і вона помре, якщо не отримає ліки, які зберігаються в її кабінеті. На жаль, у її кабінеті немає електрики і він розгерметизований.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632417</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Mikhaila</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Катерина</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632418</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Meet Mikhaila in the Coolant Monitoring station in Power Plant.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Поговорити з Катериною на електростанції, у кімнаті моніторингу систем охолодження</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632419</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Mikhaila&apos;s medicine</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Ліки Катерини</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632420</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Find Mikhaila&apos;s medicine in her office.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Знайти ліки для Катерини в її кабінеті</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632421</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Mikhaila</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Катерина</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632422</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Get the medicine to Mikhaila.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Принести ліки Катерині</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632423</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Restore power to the engineering offices.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Відновити подачу енергії в інженерні приміщення</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129891632424</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Restore power to Mikhaila&apos;s office.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Відновити подачу енергії в кабінет Катерини</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417316597511</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Chief systems engineer Mikhaila Ilyushin is hiding in the coolant monitoring room of the Power Plant. She suffers from a rare neurological condition called Paraplexis and would have died, except I managed to get her booster shots from her office. Now she plans on meeting back in my office as soon as she&apos;s recovered enough.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Головний системний інженер Катерина Ільюшина ховається на електростанції, у кімнаті моніторингу систем охолодження. У неї рідкісна хвороба, парапраксія, і вона б померла, якби мені не вдалося принести з її кабінету ліки. Вона хоче зустрітися зі мною в моєму кабінеті, коли прийде до тями.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
      <Row>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417316597917</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Chief systems engineer Mikhaila Ilyushin is hiding in the coolant monitoring room of the Power Plant. She suffered from a rare neurological condition called Paraplexis and died eventually from having no way to reach the booster shots she kept in her office.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String">Головна системна інженерка Катерина Ільюшина ховалася на електростанції, у кімнаті моніторингу систем охолодження. У неї була рідкісна хвороба, парапраксія, і вона померла, не зумівши дістатися до ліків, які зберігалися в її кабінеті.</Data>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
        <Cell>
          <Data ss:Type="String"/>
        </Cell>
      </Row>
    </Table>
  </Worksheet>
</Workbook>